本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：毒舌萌妹YY猫  蟒蛇猛汉赛太公   阿蘅阿蘅
校对：毒舌萌妹YY猫  蟒蛇猛汉赛太公  总监 YY猫
压制/特效：灰灰是菇凉   时间轴：YY猫
生
活
大
爆
炸
第八季  第十集
大家好
Hello.
我是谢尔顿·库珀博士
I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
欢迎收看由谢尔顿·库珀出品的《有趣的旗帜》
And welcome to Sheldon Cooper Presents: Fun with Flags,
最终集  壮丽的旗帜
the Final Episode Flagtacular.
我知道会有拉炮  还是吓死人家了
I knew it was coming. Still scary.
我知道你们一定在想"居然最终集了
Now, I'm sure you're thinking, "The final episode?
是谁要害你们变成旗帜盲了"
who will stand between us and flag ignorance"
像我就有这个想法
I know I was thinking that.
这是旗帜节目还是读心节目啊
Is this a show on flags or mind reading?
但事实上是因为我无法继续兼顾全职工作
But the truth is I can no longer balance a full-time career,
热门网络节目  以及女朋友了
a popular Internet show, and a girlfriend.
他是真的有女朋友  你们这些留言的混球们
And he really does have one, you jerks on the comment board.
常言道  天下无不散之筵席
So as they say, all good things must come to an end.
虽然仅有232集视觉飨宴
After only 232 episodes.
如果某人有次
233 if we include the one
没忘了按下录制键  那应该是233集
somebody forgot to press record on.
说好了不提那事儿
You said you weren't gonna bring that up.
说好了你会按录制键
And you said you pressed record.
总之  用放松的姿势
Anyway, please sit back, relax,
跟着我们一起跑完这最后一圈
and join us as we take our final lap...
就像这只赛车旗指示的一样
...as indicated by the waving of this racing flag.
白旗在不同系列车赛中有不同意义
有些代表场上有慢速车辆  有些则是最后一圈
当然  白旗也代表"举白旗投降"
And, of course, white flags can also represent surrender,
刚铎宰相  日本源氏也都使用白旗
the Stewards of Gondor, and the Japanese Minamoto clan,
刚铎宰相  《魔戒》中刚铎地区的统治者
日本源氏与平家大战时  一家白旗  一家红旗
但想必你们肯定还记得这些
but I'm sure you remember that from episode 62,
因为62集"白旗  谁举白旗及缘由"都讲过
"White Flags: Who's Wavin' 'Em and Why""
那集超赞
That was a good one.
的确是赞到爆炸
It was so good.
我本来以为清理过世教授的
You know, I thought cleaning out a dead professor's office
办公室会很无聊
was gonna just be boring,
不过在我发现他的假牙后
but then I found his dentures
我才意识到是无聊加恶心
and realized it's also gross.
艾伯特教授的家人不想要这些东西吗
Doesn't Professor Abbott's family want any of this stuff?
我记得他好像没家人
I don't think he had a family.
-真惨  -是啊
- That's rough. - I know.
一生都奉献给了工作
You can spend your whole life working,
最后留下的只有盒子里的一些研究资料
and at the end all that's left are some papers in a box.
不禁让你思索人生
Makes you think.
算了吧
Oh, well.
我们都得仔细检查过这些东西
Hey. Hey, we're supposed to look through all this stuff
以确保不会扔掉什么重要资料
before we throw it away in case it's important.
看啦  不是太旧就是被拒[反证]的
I-I did. It's all outdated or disproved.
不一定哦  这支旧笔"证明"了重力存在
I don't know. This old pen kind of proves gravity.
翻转过来  小人偶的泳衣就掉下来
When I tilt it, her bathing suit falls right off.
我爸以前也有一支这样的笔
Oh, my dad used to have a pen like that.
我整个六年级都跟它"约"会
I dated it all through sixth grade.
还是感觉很奇怪
It still feels weird
就这样把这些研究成果都扔掉
just throwing away his work like this.
不用难过
Don't feel bad.
未来某天  也会有人来扔你的研究报告
Someday, someone will be throwing out your work, too.
那个人就是谢尔顿  而那个某天是昨天
That someone was Sheldon, and the day was yesterday.
你们瞧
Hey, look at this.
"亲爱的罗杰  在你获得首次重大发现时开
"Dear Roger, to be opened upon your first great discovery.
爱你  妈"
Love, Mom."
瞧瞧这日期
Wow, look at the date.
他留了整整50年  却从没有机会开
He saved this 50 years and never got to open it.
真是让人惋惜
That's intense.
可怜的罗杰·艾伯特
Poor Roger Abbott.
罗杰特听起来像罗杰兔
Roger Abbott sounds just like Roger Rabbit.
兔子罗杰是小说与电影的一个卡通人物
罗杰特  罗杰特  罗杰兔
Roger Abbott, Roger Abbott, Roger Rabbit.
天啊  莱纳德  我知道这对死者不敬
Oh, my God, Leonard, I know he's dead,
不过你念念看  超好笑啊
but try it. It's fun!
罗杰特  罗杰特  罗杰兔
Roger Abbott, Roger Rabbit...
佩妮
Penny!
我的年度最佳新人
Oh, my rookie of the year.
丹  我一开始不想雇我
Oh, Dan. My boss who didn't want to hire me
但现在超爱抱我的老板
and now's a little hug machine.
看看你  新加入不久就业绩第三名
Oh, look at you. Brand-new and already the third best sales rep.
-过来我那桌坐坐吧  -我马上过去
- Why don't you come over to my table. - Yes. I'll be right there.
伯纳黛特还在停车
Bernadette's just parking the car.
太好了
Oh, good.
伯纳黛特  人萌音甜
Bernadette. Cute, sweet...
恶毒凶残的小伯纳黛特
vicious little Bernadette.
别这样嘛  她没那么坏
Come on. She's not that bad.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
公司野餐的时候  她吼了我跟我孙子
At the company picnic she yelled at me and my grandson
因为我们输了二人三腿赛跑
for losing the three-legged race.
我孙子现在还叫她为"毒舌大奶娃"
I mean, he still calls her "That mean kid with the big boobies."
她有时候是有点凶  但我保证
I know she can be a little intense, but, I swear,
等稍微熟了之后   她就是很亲切的一个人了
she is so sweet once you get past all the...
你们在聊什么
Hey, what are you talking about?
我们在聊有多喜欢跟你共事
We were just talking about how much we love working with you.
对吧
Isn't that right?
丹
Dan?
在《有趣的旗帜》的这些岁月里
Over the years here at Fun With Flags,
我们有机会一同学习  欢笑  惊奇
we've had an opportunity to learn, laugh, wonder...
甚至落过几滴泪
And, yes, even shed a tear or two.
比如国庆节做了两小时特别节目
Like when you do a two-hour Fourth of July spectacular
结果却没被录下来
and it doesn't get recorded.
到底要我道歉几次才够
How many times do I have to say I'm sorry?
先来个四千次吧
How about 4,000.
向我拼成美国国旗的每一片骨牌道歉
One for every domino I set up to make that American flag.
请欣赏我们的精彩剪辑
Please enjoy these highlights.
"澳"哟妈呀  今天是讲哪国的旗呢
Crikey! What flag do we have today?
澳大利亚  兄弟[澳洲口音]
Australia, mate!
现在到了高速国旗大鉴定的单元
And now it's time for the speed round of Flag or Not a Flag.
国旗  国旗
Flag. Flag.
不是国旗  国旗
Not a flag. Flag.
我太厉害了
I am crushing this.
贝特西·罗斯  你在缝什么呢
Say, Betsy Ross, what you working on?
被美国公众广泛认作美国国旗的首位缝制者
但缺乏足够的档案记载以佐证这一观点
我也不知道
I have no idea.
因为我缝出第一面美国旗帜的故事
Because the story of me sewing the first American flag
是没证据的狗屁
is unsupported poppycock.
那到底是谁缝的呢
Then who did sew it, hmm?
别问我
Don't ask me.
我只是个普通的女裁缝  是我的后代
I'm just a simple seamstress whose descendants are...
想出来坑蒙拐骗
out to make a quick buck!
赏脸共泳吗
Fancy a dip, my dear?
乐意之至
I do.
等等  紫色旗子代表了
Wait, that purple flag indicates
水域有海洋有害生物  比如毒水母
that marine pests, such as jellyfish, are present.
哇  这旗子拯"救生"命啊
Wow, that flag is a lifesaver.
不是
No.
这才是"救生"圈
This is.
别盯着人家腿了
Stop looking at my legs.
不是国旗  国旗
Not a flag. Flag.
国旗  不是国旗
Flag. Not a flag.
是的
Flag.
靠
Crap.
碰到这种让我难受的事
When stuff like this gets me down,
你知道我都怎么做吗
you know what I like to do?
像八岁小女孩一样唱"哈库那马他他"吗
Sing "Hakuna Matata" Like an eight-year-old girl?
《狮子王》电影中的欢乐歌曲
意为"不用担心"或"没有问题"
错了  自作聪明
Wrong, smarty-pants.
是《乐高大电影》里的"啥事儿都好赞"
It's "Everything Is Awesome" From The Lego Movie.
该电影中的洗脑欢乐主题曲
看这些笔记本
Look at these notebooks.
一页一页全都是数据
They're full of pages and pages of data.
明显是他多年的心血
He clearly spent years on this.
只是一行行无规律的数字  扔了吧
Oh, it's just columns of random numbers. Toss it.
万一这是他可能的重要突破呢
Well, but what if this was a potential breakthrough for him?
万一这是让能他
What if... what if this is the thing
如愿以偿打开那瓶香槟的东西呢
that would've finally let him open that bottle of champagne?
或许他不开  是因为不知道香槟要配什么
Maybe he didn't know what to pair champagne with.
草莓  鱼子酱  生蚝  都是好选择
Strawberries, caviar, oysters. All good choices.
瞧你那态度
Yeah, that look right there
所以大家才会在参加你派对前先吃饱
is why people eat before they come to your parties.
这些数据绝对是有意义的
This has to mean something.
我没能看出有什么规律啊
Well, there's no discernible pattern that I can see,
不过输进电脑里验证应该是没什么难度
but it shouldn't be too hard to run the numbers and check.
或许我们可以用超级计算机试试
Well, maybe we can get some time on the supercomputer.
可以啊  我们试试用不同的物理常数
Sure. We could try multiple regressions
与实验常数进行多元回归分析
with varying physical and experimental constants.
还可以用模式匹配算法
Oh, we could run a pattern-matching algorithm
将它们与知名未解物理问题做对比
against well-known unsolved physics problems.
甚至有可能是替换式密码
Ooh, it might be a substitution cipher.
我们可以从基本密码分析着手
We could start with basic cryptanalysis.
或者我们可以问以前跟他同一办公室的人
Or we could talk to this guy he used to share an office with.
还是那样做吧
Oh, let's do that.
因为你不知道怎么做密码分析  对吧
Because you don't know how to do cryptanalysis, do you?
我甚至不确定我说的词对不对
I'm not even sure if it's the right word.
丹  你有个孙子
So, Dan, you have a grandson.
-他几岁了  -七岁
- How old is he? - Seven.
我记得他  在那次野餐有见过
Oh, yeah. I remember him from the picnic.
一直哭个不停  像个娘娘腔似地
He was the one crying like a wuss the whole time.
我听说他是被一个小恶霸欺负了
I heard he was being picked on by a mean kid.
有助人格发展啊
Just builds character.
就像我爸说的  "没人喜欢爱哭鬼
Like my dad said, "Nobody likes a crybaby
除了他们自己的妈还有民主党"
except their mommies and Democrats."
失陪  我去加酒
I need another drink.
他是有啥不满
What's his problem?
不知道  可能他不喜欢听到
I don't know. Maybe he didn't like the fact
自己的孙子被你叫娘娘腔吧
that you called his grandson a wuss.
可现在不是不让叫别人"娘炮"吗
Well, I didn't think you were supposed to say "sissy" anymore.
我知道你这个人很好
Okay, look, I know what a good person you are,
可有时别人会觉得你表现得有点毒舌
but sometimes people think you might come off a little harsh.
什么
What?
我是我这辈子认识最甜的人了
I'm, like, the sweetest person I know.
甜得像树里做小饼干的童话人物
Look at me. I should be in a tree baking cookies.
可是有些时候
Yes, but once in a while,
有人会觉得你有点刻薄
people think you're a little mean.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
你是那些人中的一员吗
You one of those people?
不  不是不是
No. No, no, no.
我也觉得你是做饼干那种
I-I think the cookie thing.
开始
Action.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
今日的来宾曾来过  并广受观众喜欢
Our guest today is a returning fan favorite.
儿童阅读节目《阅读彩虹》的主持人
He puts the reading in your rainbow,
《星际迷航:下一代》成员
the Geordi in your La Forge,
电视迷你剧集《根》的主角
and the Kunta in your Kinte,
莱瓦尔·伯顿先生
Mr. LeVar Burton.
谢谢  谢尔顿  别忘了我们的约定
Thank you, Sheldon. Now, remember our deal...
你来上节目  我删了你的联系方式
You do this, I delete your contact information.
而且...
While...
而且是在你面前删
While you watch me do it.
很好  很高兴再来上节目
Great. Happy to be back.
既然你来了
Well, since you're here,
我想问你对某件事的看法
I'd like to get your opinion on something.
为了向黑人历史月致意
In honor of Black History Month,
赞颂黑人克服种种困难  以及对美国历史的贡献
我扮成了乔治·华盛顿·卡弗
I portrayed George Washington Carver
是美国教育家  农业化学家  植物学家
对美国有十分大贡献的一名黑人
我对他的致敬被我室友说"超有种族歧视"
in a loving tribute that my roommate called "wildly racist"
你觉得呢
What do you think?
你好  我的名字叫乔治
Hi. My name is George.
我去  不是吧
Oh, hell, no!
听到了吗  莱纳德
You heard him, Leonard.
"不是"吧  我没有种族歧视
No, it's not racist.
咱们确定是这里吗
Are we sure this is the place?
看门的说就是这栋楼
The doorman said this is the right building.
看到人来就赶紧提裤子的
I think if you're pulling up your pants,
不会是看门的  是野战的
you're not a doorman.
谁啊
Who is it?
我想找夏普教授
Uh, I'm looking for a Professor Sharpe?
等等
Hold on.
-有事吗  -您好  我们是大学的人
- Can I help you? - Hi. We're from the university.
我们想从您这打听艾伯特教授的信息
We're trying to get some information about Professor Abbott.
我们在清理他的办公室时
We were cleaning out his office
发现了一些写满数字的本子
and found these books full of numbers.
您知道这是什么吗
Any chance you know what it is?
知道  他总是在搞这玩意
Yes, he was always working on this.
我猜可能是某种星际坐标系
I was thinking it might be some sort of interstellar coordinate system,
或许是哈勃定律的升级版
maybe an updated version of Hubble's law.
哈勃定律通常被用来推算遥远星系的距离
"90"这个数字总是重复出现
I keep seeing the number 90 repeating.
那可能是某个遥远星系的摄动角度
That could be the angle of perturbation of a distant galaxy.
其实是一份酸奶的卡路里数
It's the number of calories in a yogurt.
这是他的饮食日记
That's his food diary.
真的假的
Really?
真的  他吃什么都要记下来
Yeah, he wrote down everything he ever ate.
他坚信限制卡路里摄入量
He was convinced that calorie restriction
是长命百岁的关键
was the key to living forever.
那管用吗
Does it work?
你闹呢
Seriously?
他可能是死于车祸啊  你又不知道
Well, he could have been hit by a bus. You don't know.
抱歉  真相不是那么有趣
Sorry it's not more interesting.
往好的方面想  你们不必听
On the bright side, you didn't have to listen
他35年来肚子饿得咕噜叫的声音
to his stomach growl for 35 years.
那艾伯特教授这辈子研究的东西
So, was there anything that Professor Abbott worked on
难道没有半点算得上是成就的东西吗
during his life that came close to an accomplishment?
老实说  他的研究一无所成
To be honest, his research never amounted to anything.
你是他的同事
Oh. You were his colleague.
你的研究结果如何
How did your research turn out?
很棒
Great.
得诺贝尔奖的人  都住这种"豪宅"
Hey, this is the apartment you get when you win a Nobel.
你可以是一个很简朴的人啊
Well, you could be very frugal.
我真是受够了每个人都在说反话了
I'm getting a little tired of everybody's sarcasm.
我不是恶霸
I'm not a bully.
或许我是表现得有那么一点强势
I mean, maybe I come off a little strong,
但那只是因为我父亲从小教育我要强硬
but that's only because my dad raised me to be tough
不要随便受人欺负
and not to take crap from anybody.
那当然可以啊
No. That's fine,
但强硬跟告诉你的朋友
but there's a difference between being tough
她的新裤子像一块松垮的尿布
and telling your friend her new pants
这两者还是有区别的
look like a saggy diaper.
我的确那么说了  是吧
I did say that, didn't I?
是的  你说了
Yeah, you did.
我当时超级难为情  我只好把裤子退了
I felt so self-conscious, I had to return them.
退到哪儿  婴儿用品店吗
Where? To Babies R Us?
你又来了
You're doing it again!
对不起  我们可以走了吗
Okay, sorry. Can we just go?
我感觉大家都讨厌我
I feel like everybody hates me.
别这样  他们不讨厌你  好吗
Oh, come on, they don't hate you, all right?
他们只是有点怕你而已
They're just a little intimidated.
你只需让大家看到
All you need to do is show everyone
你其实非常亲切
how sweet you really are.
-我还是走吧  -不  坐下
- I think I'd rather go. - No, come on.
你哪儿也不许去  知道吗
You are not going anywhere, all right?
我在这陪着你  我们一起来解决这问题
I am here for you, and we are gonna fix this together.
谢谢
Thank you.
虽然你今天的裙子很难看
Even though your dress is ugly.
我的小旗友们
Well, my little Flag-keteers,
最后一集《有趣的旗帜》就要结束了
it looks like the last episode of Fun with Flags is at an end.
如果可以
If I could,
你们每个人都是我升上去后
I would run each and every one of you viewers up a flagpole
原俗语直翻为"升到旗杆上  看看有没有人会敬礼"
意思是试试水  看看反应的意思
愿意敬礼的旗帜
and salute you.
如果你掉到地面  我会烧掉你
And if you touched the ground, burn you.
根据规定  美国国旗降旗时  不能触碰地面
如果国旗被弄脏或要退役  得庄重处理  通常烧毁
我想花一点时间
I'd like to take a moment
亲自谢谢艾米·费拉·福勒博士
to personally thank Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler,
你们或许知道  也或许不知道
who you may or may not know
她是第一位搭档主持关于旗帜
is the first woman to co-host a flag
或横幅相关的网络寓教于乐节目的女性
or banner-related Internet info-tainment show.
听见了吗  玻璃天花板
Take that, glass ceiling.
玻璃天花板是指女性和少数族裔无法晋升到决策层的无形障碍
请容许我认真地说几句
And if I may get serious for a moment,
主持这档节目
hosting this show has been...
是一段疯狂的旅程
one crazy ride.
一路走来的高兴与失落
With all its ups and downs,
是我无论如何都不想放弃的
I wouldn't give it up for the world.
除了现在  我要放弃这节目了
Except for now, when I'm giving it up.
在节目正式停播前  我想...
Before I sign off, I'd, uh...
我想跟大家分享白旗的最后一个用处
I'd like to share with you all one last use for a white flag.
像这种时候  可以拿来擦眼泪
It's good for times like this.
晚安
Good night.
停
Cut.
谢尔顿
Sheldon...
刚才那段话太感人了
that was beautiful.
如果你没有按下录制...
If you didn't press record...
老娘按了
I pressed it!
结束了
Well, that's it.
罗杰·艾伯特的东西清理完毕
That's the end of Roger Abbott.
我们仍不知道是谁陷害了他
And we still don't know who framed him.
兔子罗杰的电影名为《谁陷害了兔子罗杰》
我一直在思考  一个人的一生
I still keep thinking about how an entire life
怎么能一无所成呢
can seemingly amount to nothing.
事实就是这么悲哀
I guess the sad truth is,
不是所有人都能功成名就
not everyone will accomplish something great.
我们中有些人注定要在
Some of us may just have to find meaning
日常生活的点滴中寻找生命的意义
in the little moments that make up life.
这个看待的方法很不错
That's a nice way of looking at it.
对你而言是  我可不是
Yeah for you, not for me.
哥上过太空呢  此生足矣
I went to space. I'm covered.
不如这样
You know what?
这瓶香槟本来就是要庆祝成就的
This bottle was meant to celebrate an achievement.
我们做个约定
Let's make a pact.
当我们中有人获得人生中第一次重大突破时
When one of us gets their first big breakthrough,
我们就打开这瓶香槟庆祝
we'll celebrate by opening this bottle of champagne
并向罗杰·艾伯特致敬
and toasting Professor Abbott.
我喜欢这主意
I love that.
我也是
Yeah, me, too.
当然还包括
Then, of course,
向谢尔顿炫耀我们的成果
rubbing our success in Sheldon's face.
-这是最精彩的部分  -没错
- Oh, well, that's the best part. - Oh, yeah.
丹  我能和你聊聊吗
Dan, could I talk to you for a minute?
好的  说吧
Sure, go ahead.
我只是想告诉你
Just want you to know I didn't mean
我不是故意侮辱你的孙子
to be rude about your grandson.
没关系
No, it's okay.
不  有关系
No, it's not.
佩妮告诉我  大家都怕我
Penny told me that everyone's scared of me.
怎么会  怎么会
What? What?
她为什么那么说
Why would she say that?
-你知道她是酒鬼  会乱说话吧  -少来
- You know she drinks, right? - What?
不  她说得对  我要让你知道
No, she's right, and I just want you to know
从现在起  我会多体会大家心情
that from now on, I'm gonna be much more sensitive.
我不想让大家在我面前如履薄冰
I don't want anyone walking on eggshells around me.
那好吧  有件事
Oh, well, okay, then, uh,
我一直想告诉你
one thing I've been meaning to tell you
公司不再给我们提供免费的咖啡了
is that the company is gonna stop paying for our coffee.
没问题  什么时候开始
No problem. When does that start?
五个月前
Five months ago.
-什么  -没错
- What?! - Yeah.
那我的咖啡一直都是谁买的
Who's been paying for my coffee?
我们大伙儿
All of us.
买咖啡的钱来自你一骂人
Yeah. It comes from the swear jar
我们就投钱进去的那个脏话罐
we put money in when you curse.
还有什么事是我不知道的
What else don't I know about?
-你的私人卫生间  -怎么了
- Uh, well, you know your private bathroom? - Yeah?
那应该是给整层楼的人使用的
That was supposed to be for the whole floor.
-你开什么玩笑  -那个无所谓
- You're kidding. - No, no. It's okay.
其实只对轮椅妹凯西有影响
It only really affected wheelchair Kathy,
现在她已经回医院了
and she's back in the hospital now,
所以没什么问题了
so it all worked out.
我感觉好难过哦
I feel so bad.
那你就不应该给人家取名"轮椅妹凯西"啊
Well, then, maybe you shouldn't have named her "Wheelchair Kathy."
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
我以为大家都喜欢我  其实我只是个怪兽
I thought everybody liked me, but I'm just a monster.
但很可爱呀  就像《怪兽公司》里的独眼怪
But a cute one, like that, uh, eyeball guy in Monsters, Inc.
不  我最坏了
No, I'm the worst.
我是个坏人
I'm a terrible person.
乖  别哭  没关系啦
Come on, don't cry. It's okay.
有关系
It's not okay.
我哪还有脸留在这工作呀
How can I even work here anymore? Oh.
-这家公司需要你  -真没事
- Because this company needs you. - It's fine.
我们不介意给你买咖啡
We don't mind paying for the coffee.
我不能让你们这么做
I can't let you do that.
或许我们可以给你
Maybe we could get you
买一台咖啡机放在你办公室里
an espresso machine for your office.
-这样也行吧  -好的
- I guess that would be all right. - All right.
瞧  你不刻薄也能得到你想要的东西
See? You don't have to be mean to get what you want.
此话有理
You're right.
那我的私人卫生间现在怎么处理呢
Now where did we land on my bathroom?
好啊
Hi.
回来啦
Hello.
这么晚还不睡吗
How come you're up so late?
我上传《有趣的旗帜》最终集好几个小时了
I posted the last episode of Fun with Flags hours ago,
没有任何人在乎到愿意留个言
and not a single person cared enough to comment.
一切努力都是徒然
All that effort for nothing.
我明白你的感受
I know how you feel.
我今天一天把一个男人一生事业扔进垃圾桶
I spent the day throwing out a man's entire career,
唯一留下的是一瓶陈年香槟
and all that's left is an old bottle of champagne
和拉杰自以为没人发现
and a naked lady pen that Raj took
就私吞了的一根裸女笔
when he thought no one was looking.
这根本是两码事
It's not the same thing.
你完全不明白我的感受
I don't think you know how I feel at all.
是难过吗
Sad?
看来你真的懂我
You do get me.
有人留言了
Someone left a comment.
他们说什么
Yeah. What did they say?
"你的节目结束了真可惜
"Too bad your show is done.
我还挺喜欢的"
I kind of liked it."
莱纳德  你听到了吗
Leonard, did you hear that?
网友们难过得要死
Oh, the people are heartbroken!
这世界上不能没有这节目
I can't take this away from the world!
《有趣的旗帜》满血复活了
Fun with Flags is back!
恭喜
Congratulations.
我们来庆祝吧
Let's celebrate!
谢尔顿  那不是给你的
Sheldon, that wasn't for you!
我也没打算喝啊
Oh, no, I'm not going to drink it.
我只想听开瓶那砰的一声
I just wanted to hear the pop.
我知道会砰的一声  还是吓死人家了
Yeah, I knew it was coming. Still scary.
莱瓦尔·伯顿
LeVar Burton?
LeVar Burton!
莱瓦尔·伯顿
你来干嘛
What are you doing here?
你不让我打电话给你
You told me not to call,
我不知道该怎么告诉你这个好消息
and I didn't know how else to give you the good news.
《有趣的旗帜》回归了
Fun with Flags is back,
下一集你可以来当嘉宾
and you can be in the next episode.
威尔·惠顿让我弄个大闸门
Wil Wheaton said, get a gate.
-我当初真该听他的话  -你真是...
- I don't know why I didn't get a gate. - You...
至少你听我说完前提
At least listen to the premise.
既然你在德国出生
Since you were born in Germany,
我们可以聊聊德国国旗
I thought we could talk about German flags.
你有兴趣装扮成卐字图案吗
How do you feel about dressing up like a swastika?
德国纳粹旗  该卐与佛教的卍相反